Chris Griffin 10 Royal Park Avenue Leeds LS6 1EY Tel. 07523120892

Email: chrisgriffin2001@icloud.com

Profile

I have been learning to code using Swift with X-code Beta for around a year, I've also made some basic apps with simple user interfaces. I was completing a Bachelor of Engineering degree (Honours), but on reflection I am not sure if this is the correct career choice for me at this present time. I originally trained as an Electrician to which I am qualified and registered, I also have over thirteen years' experience within the electrical industry and with a strong customer facing background. I am always willing to learn new skills.

Key skills

- Active Listening
- Communication
- Computer Skills
- Customer Service
- Interpersonal Skills
- Leadership
- Management Skills
- Problem-Solving
- Time Management
- Transferable Skills

Employment History

Jan 2011-May 2013

Working for BT/Openreach (Field Engineer) through Hays on a temp contract, day to day duties at Openreach involve a face to face customer role installing and maintaining phone lines on the network.

May 2013- August 2013

For this period I worked for Search recruitment agency on a new-build NHS facility in Harrogate for cancer outpatients. My duties there were first fix and some second.

August 2013- Present

Working for Skipton properties Ltd, I have been working as a Scaffolder/ Supervisor on a full-time basis while I completed my Bachelor of Engineering degree (Honours). Day to day duties include erection and dismantling scaffold, arranging plant work for future projects and costing work within our team.

Education

Higher education

The Open University
2013 – present
Currently working towards Bachelor of Engineering (Honours)

Further education

City & Guilds

Signing, lighting and guarding.

NVQ Level 3-Installing and Commissioning Electrotechnical Systems and Equipment.

BS 7671 (16 edition).

Level 3 Certificate of Competence for the Inspection and Testing of Electrical Equipment

(PAT Testing).

Achievement Measurement 2 (AM 2) Passed.

Compulsory secondary education

GCSE'S

Math C English C Science D

Other

Domestic Installer Scheme Qualification Part P.

CRB cleared.

SWQR (street works)

CAL (BT accredited)

Working at Heights (BT accredited)

Hobbies and interests

In my free time I enjoy spending time with my family, reading, learning languages, going to Gym and spending most of my spare time coding.

References available on request.